- Oh, every night
- Hold tight
SHELDON:
Baby, hold tight
[IN UNISON]
Any way you want it
That's the way you need it
Oh, whoa
(Leonard:)All right, Mother.
(Leonard:)- Um, have a nice flight.
- That's not really in my control, is it?
(Beverley:)Oh, uh, yes.
- Oh, good morning.
- Morning.
(Penny:)- I was just coming over to talk to you...
- You don't have to.
(Leonard's Mother:)Ever.
(Penny:)Gotcha.
- Goodbye, Mother.
- Goodbye, Leonard.
(Beverley:)So, slugger, shall we pick up
where we left off last time?
[PENNY SOBBING]
(Penny(in tears):)I mean, my mom could've just said,
"Bob, get over it, she's a girl, move on."
(Penny(in tears):)But she didn't. Not one word.
(Beverley:)Interesting. Would you be willing
to fly to New Jersey...
(Beverley:)...and discuss your relationship
with your parents during a brain scan?
- Would it help?
- Well, it would help me.